Finding Aid for the Honey Alexander Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Series II: Healthy Children Initiative
  - First Lady – Healthy Children Initiative, 1982-1987
    - “Your Body Book”, 1984 September (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - “Healthy Children for the Future of Tennessee”, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - “Don’t Take Their Health for Granted”, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - “The Healthy Children Activity Book”, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Newsletter, 1984-1985 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Health Curriculum Guide K-5, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Health Curriculum Guide 6-12, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - First Lady – Healthy Children Initiative, 1982-1987
    - Promotional Posters, undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Progress Report – circa, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Memo to Manny Martins, 1984 November 6 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Letter to Marc Lavine from Honey, 1984 September 24 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Gonorrhea in Pre-pubertal Children, 1984 September (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - News, 1984 September (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Memo to Social Environment Subcommittee, 1984 August 31 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Newsletter, 1984 May-June (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - News – circa, 1984 March 21 – April 28 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Nutrition Activities, undated (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Programs Summary, undated (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Regional Perinatal Center Activities and Fact Sheet, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Letter, 1984 March 20 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Healthy Children Booklet Year Two: Infant Follow-up, 1984-1985 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Symposium at East Tennessee State University, 1984 June (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Health Children Fact Sheet, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Suggestions for Community Action, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Social Environment Subcommittee Minutes, 1985 January 30 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Final Recommendations, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Task Force Meeting Highlights, 1985 January 30 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Policy Recommendations, 1985 Winter (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Legislative Report, 1985 February 22 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Form Letter by James Word: Healthy Children, 1985 March (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - News Release on Gallup Poll on Birth Control, 1985 March 6 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - EPSDT – Your Child’s Ticket to Health Care, 1985 March (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Letter to Health Care Professionals from Comm. James Wood, 1985 March (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Media Information, 1985 April (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Medical Home Subcommittee Meeting Notes, 1985 May 10 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Agenda: Task Force, 1985 May 22 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Update – Genetics, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Tennessee Infant Mortality Fact Sheet, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Healthy Children Evaluation Plan, 1985 July 30 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Memo re: SPRANS Grant, 1985 August 5 (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - Volunteers for Healthy Children – Focus: Abused and Neglected Children, 1985 August (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - Volunteers for Healthy Children – Focus: Children with Handicaps, 1985 August (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - Volunteers for Healthy Children – Focus: Pregnant Teenagers, 1985 August (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - Volunteers for Healthy Children – Focus: New Parents and Babies, 1985 August (Box 35, Folder 37)
    - Facets Article on Teen Pregnancy, 1985 September (Box 35, Folder 38)
    - Memo to Social Environment Subcommittee Members from Joe McLaughlin, 1985 November 5 (Box 35, Folder 39)
    - Healthy Children Booklet Year 3: Infant Follow-up, 1985-1986 (Box 35, Folder 40)
    - List of Task Force Members, 1986 March 14 (Box 35, Folder 41)
  - First Lady – Healthy Children Initiative, 1982-1987
    - Progress Report, 1986 Spring (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Introductory Remarks – Susie Baird, 1986 September 15 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Honey and William H. Brown re: Susan Gray School for Children, 1986 October (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Memo to Task Force on Final Recommendations, 1986 November 21 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Possible Changes in Task Force Recommendations, 1986 December 8 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Final Recommendations: Task Force, 1986 December (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Honey and Richard Swiggart, 1987 January (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Speeches, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Notebook – First Year Implementation, 1983-1984 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Notebook – First Year Implementation, 1983-1984 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Notebook – First Year Implementation, 1983-1984 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- Series III: Task Force on Mental Retardation Prevention
  - Series III: Task Force on Mental Retardation Prevention, 1980-1984
    - Background, 1980-1981 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Background, 1980-1981 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Tennessee Volunteers for Children, 1981-1982 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Tennessee Volunteers for Children, 1981-1982 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Tennessee Volunteers for Children, 1981-1982 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - President’s and Virginia’s Reports on Prevention, 1980-1981 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Susie Baird Correspondence, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - First Lady – Task Force on Mental Retardation Prevention, 1980-1984
    - High Risk Subcommittee, s1981-1984 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Family Life Subcommittee, 1983-1984 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Summary of Recommendations Correspondence, 1981 December (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - General, 1981-1985 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Association for Retarded Citizens, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Association for Retarded Citizens, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, 1982 January 12 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, 1982 March 4 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Meeting, 1982 June 21 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Meeting, 1982 August 23 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Mental Health Resources – Knox County, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Mental Health Resources – Union City, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Mental Health Resources – Newport – Cocke County, 1981-1982 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Mental Health Resources – Johnson City – Sullivan, 1981-1982 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Mental Health Resources – Jasper – Marion, 1981-1982 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Mental Health Resources – Sevier County, 1980-1981 (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Series IV: Subject Files
  - First Lady – Subject Files – Alcohol and Drug Abuse, 1984-1985
    - Armes – Clark (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Coker – Fleisher (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Governor’s Task Force – Reports (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Governor’s Task Force – Reports (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Governor’s Task Force – Reports (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Governor’s Task Force – Reports (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Governor’s Task Force, 1984 December 6 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Governor’s Task Force, 1984 December 18 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Governor’s Task Force, 1985 January 8 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Governor’s Task Force, 1985 January 10 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Governor’s Task Force, 1985 January 16 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Governor’s Task Force, 1985 January 18-24 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Governor’s Task Force, 1985 January 29 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Governor’s Task Force, 1985 February 13 – April 21 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Governor’s Task Force, 1985 May 23 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Governor’s Task Force, 1985 June (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Governor’s Task Force, 1985 June (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Governor’s Task Force, 1985 June (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Griffith – Heywood (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Hooper – Indian Path Pavilion (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Jacobs – Mahoney (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Johnson City Minutes (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Johnson City Minutes (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Paar – Public Health Service (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Reynolds (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Schmutzer – Tennessee (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Tennesseans Against Drugs – Tennessee Municipal League (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - “A Woman Who Drinks” – “Youth Alcohol and Drug Abuse” (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - First Lady – Subject Files, 1985-1986
    - “Youth Alcohol and Drug Abuse – A Special Report to the Governor”, 1985 July (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Youth Alcohol and Drug Abuse, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Just Say No, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Just Say No, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Just Say No, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Tennessee Homecoming 1986 – Gladeville Elementary School Students Art Book, 1986 March 4 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Tennessee Homecoming 1986 – Gladeville Elementary School Students Art Book, 1986 March 4 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Tennessee Homecoming 1986 – Gladeville Elementary School Students Art Book, 1986 March 4 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Tennessee Homecoming 1986 – Gladeville Elementary School Students Art Book, 1986 March 4 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Tennessee Homecoming 1986 – Gladeville Elementary School Students Art Book, 1986 March 4 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - First Lady – Subject Files, 1984-1986
    - People to People, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Teen Pregnancy, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Teen Pregnancy, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Teen Pregnancy, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Southern Regional Task Force on Infant Mortality – General, 1984-1985 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Southern Regional Task Force on Infant Mortality – General, 1984-1985 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Southern Regional Task Force on Infant Mortality – General, 1984-1985 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - First Lady – Subject Files, 1978-1986
    - Southern Regional Task Force on Infant Mortality – General, 1985-1986 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Southern Regional Task Force on Infant Mortality – General, 1985-1986 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Southern Regional Task Force on Infant Mortality – Final Report, 1985 November (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Executive Residence Preservation Foundation, 1978-1982 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Guest Lists, 1979-1982 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Guest Lists, 1979-1982 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Guest Lists, 1979-1982 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Governor’s Mansion – Tennessee Federation of Women’s Clubs, 1980-1982 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Governor’s Mansion – Renovation, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - First Lady – Subject Files, 1979-1985
    - Auction of Executive Residence Furnishings, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Publications – “Edmondson’s Art Reflects His Faith, Strong and Pure” – circa, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Publications – Carroll Cloar: The Tennessee Years, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Publications – Holston Mental Health Center, 1979 June (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Publications – Spectrum, 1979 May (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Publications – Cumberland, 1979 Winter (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Publications – Breakthrough, 1979 Spring – 1985 Winter (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Publications – Spectrum, 1980 February-March (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Publications – Architectural Digest, 1985 December (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Testimony to U.S. Senate Committee on Labor and Human Resources, 1983 November 16 (1 of 6) (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Testimony to U.S. Senate Committee on Labor and Human Resources, 1983 November 16 (2 of 6) (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Testimony to U.S. Senate Committee on Labor and Human Resources, 1983 November 16 (3 of 6) (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Testimony to U.S. Senate Committee on Labor and Human Resources, 1983 November 16 (4 of 6) (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Testimony to U.S. Senate Committee on Labor and Human Resources, 1983 November 16 (5 of 6) (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Testimony to U.S. Senate Committee on Labor and Human Resources, 1983 November 16 (6 of 6) (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence – Republican Governor’s Association, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Heads Up Child Development Center, 1980 July-September (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Heads Up Child Development Center, 1981-1982 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Lupus Society, 1978-1980 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - The Week of the Young Child, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - The Week of the Young Child, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Box">First Lady – Subject Files, 1979-1984
    - White House Conference on Children and Youth, 1980-1981 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - The Assault Against Cancer Among Blacks, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Torch Run, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Portland, Tennessee Trip, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - UT Center for the Health Sciences, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Monroe Maternity Center, 1984 May (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Christmas Party, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Christmas Party, 1985 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Inaugural File, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - National Governor’s Association – General, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - National Governor’s Association – General, 1984 Summer (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - National Governor’s Association – General, 1984 Summer (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - First Lady – Subject Files, 1979-1984
    - National Governor’s Association – Bills, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - National Governor’s Association – Youth and Spouse Programs, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Interview Schedule / AA Job Search, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Needlepoint, 1979-1980 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - United Way and Council of Community Services, 1982-1983 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Committee of Visitors for Vanderbilt School of Nursing, 1982-1983 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Committee of Visitors for Vanderbilt School of Nursing, 1982-1983 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Revenue Received, 1983-1984 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Council of Community Services – General, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Council of Community Services – General, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Tennessee Council for the Hearing Impaired, 1980-1981 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - First Lady – Subject Files, 1978-1981
    - White House Conference on Families, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - White House Conference on Families, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - White House Conference on Families – Reports, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - White House Conference on Families – Tennessee Conference Planning, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - White House Conference on Families – Delegate Selection, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Tennessee Association for Retarded Citizens, 1980-1981 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Tennessee Association for Retarded Citizens, 1980-1981 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Tennessee Personnel and Guidance Association, 1978-1980 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Mental Health – Memphis, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Lung Association, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Tennessee Women’s Career Convention, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Meeting with Children and Youth Services, 1979 April 5-6 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - First Lady – Subject Files, 1978-1980
    - International Year of the Child, 1978-1980 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - International Year of the Child, 1978-1980 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - International Year of the Child, 1978-1980 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - International Year of the Child, 1978-1980 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - International Year of the Child, 1978-1980 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Group Service for Girls, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Interdepartmental Conference – Department of Human Services, Department of Correction, and Department of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, 1980 January (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Comprehensive Emergency Services, 1979 December (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Tennessee Children’s Services Commission, 1980 December (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Juvenile Detention, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - First Lady – Subject Files, 1980-1984
    - Dede Wallace Center, 1982-1984 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Dede Wallace Center, 1982-1984 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Runaways Task Force, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Address and Telephone Logs, 1979-1982 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Address and Telephone Logs, 1979-1982 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Address and Telephone Logs, 1979-1982 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Craftsmakers and Contacts, 1983-1984 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Craftsmakers and Contacts, 1983-1984 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Craftsmakers and Contacts, 1983-1984 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Craftsmakers and Contacts, 1983-1984 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Craftsmakers and Contacts, 1983-1984 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Craftsmakers and Contacts, 1983-1984 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Cades Cove / Thanksgiving, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Christmas Lists, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Christmas Lists, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Christmas Lists, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Christmas Cards, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Christmas Cards, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Executive Residence, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - First Lady – Subject Files, 1979-1986
    - Children Services Legislation, 1979-1980 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - White House Conference on Families – General, 1980 March (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Tennessee State Museum, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Just Say “No”, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Governor’s Awards in the Arts, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - National Governor’s Association – General, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - National Governor’s Association – General, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - National Governor’s Association – General, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - National Governor’s Association – Spouse’s Resource Book, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - National Governor’s Association – “On Being a Governor’s Spouse…” – circa, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Southern Governor’s Association, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Southern Governor’s Association, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - First Lady – Subject Files, 1960-1990
    - Elementary School Guidance and Counseling, 1980 February-April (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - PTA – Child Immunization, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Immunizations, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Information and Referral, 1979-1980 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - St. Jude Reception, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Notes and Materials, 1960-1990 (1 of 2) (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Notes and Materials, 1960-1990 (1 of 2) (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Notes and Materials – circa, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Series V: Events and Invitations
  - First Lady – Events and Invitations, 1985
    - Dinner Invitations for Honoring the Governors of States and Territories, 1985 February (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - First Lady – Events and Invitations, 1979-1985
    - Governor’s Mansion, 1981-1982 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Honey’s Surprise 40th Birthday Party (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - TAYC Annual Conference, 1981 September-October (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Foothills Craft Guild, Inc. 1981 Show and Sale, 1981 October-November (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Center for Southern Folklore, 1981 October 8-13 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Residence Events, 1980-1982 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Residence Events – Birthday Dinner, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Residence Events – State Dinner, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Residence Events – State Dinner, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Residence Events – State Dinner, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Residence Events – Chinese Reception, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Residence Events – Cumberland Heights Luncheon, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Residence Events – Education Reception, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Residence Events – Freshmen Legislators’ Luncheon, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Residence Events – Gannet Dinner, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Residence Events – Hoglund Dinner, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Residence Events – Legislature Reception, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Residence Events – Patterson Dinner, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Residence Events – Reception for Tennessee Press Association, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Residence Events – Rodgers Dinner, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Residence Events – Spring Cabinet Dinner, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Residence Events – State Dinner, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Residence Events – State Dinner, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - Residence Events – Transplants Reception, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 24)
    - Residence Events – Transplants Reception, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - First Lady – Events and Invitations, 1979-1985
    - Entertainment at the Residence, 1986 January-February (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Alex Haley Lunch, 1986 January (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Dinner in Honor of Thomas Garland, 1986 February 4 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Birthday Group Party, 1986 February 18 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Southern Leadership Reception, 1986 February 26 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Tennessee Homecoming Reception, 1986 April 6 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Cabinet Dinner, 1986 May 10 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Japan Dinner, 1986 May 23 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - June Entertainment Schedule, 1986 June (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Birthday Group, 1986 July 22 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Governor’s Awards, 1986 July-August (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - State Dinner – Moffitt and Whittle, 1986 August-October (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Southern Legislator’s Conference, 1986 November (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Invitations and Menus, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Invitations and Menus, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Invitations and Menus, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Invitations and Menus, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Invitations and Menus, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Invitations and Menus, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Invitations and Menus, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 20)
- Series VI: Speeches
  - Series VI: Speeches, 1979-1983
    - Juv. Cat. Workers Conference, 1979 July (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - General, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - “Families” – Governor’s Conference on Families, 1980 February (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Child Advocacy, 1980 February 12 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - “Families” – FHA Meeting, 1980 April 16 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Tennessee Guidance and Personnel Association, 1980 May 1 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Overlook Mental Health Speech, 1980 June 9 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Information and Referral Conference, 1980 June 13 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Shelbyville, 1980 July 9 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - WACF Speech to Child and Family Services, 1980 September 22 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - “Responsibilities of Tennessee’s First Lady”, 1980 October 22 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Tennessee Conference on Social Welfare – Johnson City, 1980 October 23 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Building Bridges – Knoxville, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Tomorrow’s Children – Spain, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Legislative Campaign Speech for Jean Howard, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Brentwood Rotary Club, 1981 February 13 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Tennessee Behavior Therapy Association, 1981 March 24 – April 3 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Bride and Groom Show, 1981 March 28 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Nashville Junior League, 1981 May (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Mental Health Association of Knox County, 1981 May 7 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - GOP Women – Nashville, 1981 May 13 (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - 27th Annual Meeting of National Conference of Women in Chambers of Commerce, 1981 October 23 (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - Cookeville ARC – circa, 1981 September 27 (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - Parents Pleas. – UT Martin, 1981 October 23 (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - GOP Women – Chattanooga, 1981 October 27 (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - National Association of Social Workers, 1981 October – November (Box 53, Folder 26)
    - General, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 27)
    - Children and Families – circa, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 28)
    - Junior League of Memphis, 1981-1982 (Box 53, Folder 29)
    - Spring Hill High School Speech, 1982 May 11 (Box 53, Folder 30)
    - Northwest Tennessee Mental Health Center, 1982 May 24 (Box 53, Folder 31)
    - “Gaps in Children’s Services”, 1982 July 21 (Box 53, Folder 32)
    - Mental Retardation and DD Directors – Fall Creek Falls, 1982 August (Box 53, Folder 33)
    - Permanency Planning Conference, 1982 September (Box 53, Folder 34)
    - Nutrition Council of Chattanooga, 1982 September 28 – October 1 (Box 53, Folder 35)
    - Mental Retardation Prevention, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 36)
    - Baird-Edwards, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 37)